Guide to the Professional Staff Congress/City University of New York Records WAG.009
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series III: Records of the Professional Staff Congress, 1926-2016; 108492
  - Subseries III:B: Officers and Staff Files, 1926-2009; 378005
    - Sub Subseries III:B:1: Aaron Alexander Files, 1948-1997, 109753
      - Tuition: Tax Credits, etc., 1979; 109784 (Box 32, Folder 14)
      - Tuition: Tax Credits, etc., 1980-1989; 109783 (Box 32, Folder 15)
      - Tuition: Tax Cuts, 1981-1984; 109782 (Box 32, Folder 16)
      - Unemployment Insurance, 1978-1979; 109781 (Box 32, Folder 17)
      - United Federation of Teachers (UFT), undated, 1971-1976; 109780 (Box 32, Folder 18)
      - UFT, 1977-1978; 109779 (Box 32, Folder 19)
      - UFT, 1979-1986; 109778 (Box 32, Folder 20)
      - UFT: Oral History Project, 1983-1984; 109777 (Box 32, Folder 21)
      - United University Professors (UUP), 1971-1977; 109776 (Box 32, Folder 22)
      - UUP, 1978; 109775 (Box 33, Folder 1)
      - UUP, 1979-1988; 109774 (Box 33, Folder 2)
      - Urban University Act, undated, 1965, 1977-1978; 109773 (Box 33, Folder 3)
      - Visitors, undated, 1987-1990; 109772 (Box 33, Folder 4)
      - Voorhees Technical Institute, 1968, 1977-1986; 109771 (Box 33, Folder 5)
      - Welfare Fund, undated, 1976-1978; 109770 (Box 33, Folder 6)
      - Welfare Fund, 1979-1980; 109769 (Box 33, Folder 7)
      - Welfare Fund, 1982-1986; 109768 (Box 33, Folder 8)
      - Welfare Fund Newsletters, 1968-1989; 109767 (Box 33, Folder 9)
      - Why Go To College?: AFT Edition, undated, 1980-1981; 109766 (Box 33, Folder 10)
      - Why Go To College?: Budget, undated, 1978-1980; 109765 (Box 33, Folder 11)
      - Why Go To College?: Comments, undated, 1980-1985; 109764 (Box 33, Folder 12)
      - Why Go To College?: Photos, Releases, undated, 1978-1985; 109763 (Box 33, Folder 13)
      - Why Go To College?: Publicity, undated, 1978-1980; 109762 (Box 33, Folder 14)
      - Workload, 1973-1985; 109761 (Box 33, Folder 15)
      - Workload, undated; 109760 (Box 33, Folder 16)
      - Yeshiva Decision, undated, 1978-1980; 109759 (Box 33, Folder 17)
      - Yeshiva Decision, 1981-1994; 109758 (Box 33, Folder 18)
      - York College, undated, 1976-1987; 109757 (Box 33, Folder 19)
      - Zeller, Belle: Biographical File, undated, 1940-1994; 109756 (Box 33, Folder 20)
      - Zeller, Belle: Oral History, 1985; 109755 (Box 33, Folder 21)
      - Zeller, Belle: Scholarship Fund, undated, 1979, 1989-1991; 109754 (Box 33, Folder 22)
    - Sub Subseries III:B:2: Claude Campbell Files, 1974-1984, 109749
      - Campbell, Claude: Memos, 1974-1977; 109752 (Box 34, Folder 1)
      - Campbell, Claude: Memos, 1978; 109751 (Box 34, Folder 2)
      - Campbell, Claude: Memos, 1979-1984; 109750 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Sub Subseries III:B:3: Irwin Polishook Files, 1969-2000, 109308
      - Abzug, Bella, 1977; 109748 (Box 34, Folder 4)
      - Academic Due Process, 1975; 109747 (Box 34, Folder 5)
      - Academic Freedom, undated, 1973-1977; 109746 (Box 34, Folder 6)
      - Academic Freedom, 1979-1981; 109745 (Box 34, Folder 7)
      - Academic Freedom, 1993-1994, 1999; 109744 (Box 34, Folder 8)
      - Academic Program Planning, 1994-1995; 109743 (Box 34, Folder 9)
      - Academic Standards (CUNY), undated, 1997; 109742 (Box 34, Folder 10)
      - Accountability, 1991-1994; 109741 (Box 34, Folder 11)
      - Adelphi University, 1996; 109740 (Box 34, Folder 12)
      - Adjuncts, 1973-1984; 109739 (Box 34, Folder 13)
      - Adjuncts, 1989-1998; 109738 (Box 34, Folder 14)
      - Administrative Council, 1973; 109737 (Box 34, Folder 15)
      - Administration: Meetings with PSC, 1978; 109736 (Box 34, Folder 16)
      - Admissions Policy, 1975; 109735 (Box 34, Folder 17)
      - Affirmative Action, 1975-1979; 109734 (Box 34, Folder 18)
      - Agency Fee, 1977-1982, 1997; 109733 (Box 34, Folder 19)
      - Agreement, 1973; 109732 (Box 34, Folder 20)
      - Agreement, 1976; 109731 (Box 34, Folder 21)
      - Agreement, 1978; 109730 (Box 34, Folder 22)
      - Alexander, Aaron, 1974-1979; 109729 (Box 34, Folder 23)
      - American Association of University Professors (AAUP), 1976-1980; 109728 (Box 34, Folder 24)
      - AAUP, 1981; 109727 (Box 34, Folder 25)
      - AAUP, undated; 109726 (Box 34, Folder 26)
      - AAUP, 1992-1999; 109725 (Box 34, Folder 27)
      - American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO): Public Education Department, 1993; 109724 (Box 34, Folder 28)
      - American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees (AFSCME), District Council 37, Local 384, 1972-1977; 109723 (Box 34, Folder 29)
      - American Federation of Teachers (AFT), 1973-1979; 109722 (Box 34, Folder 30)
      - AFT, 1980-1984; 109721 (Box 35, Folder 1)
      - AFT, 1988-1994; 109720 (Box 35, Folder 2)
      - AFT, 1995-2000; 109719 (Box 35, Folder 3)
      - Annunziato, Frank, 1995-1999; 109718 (Box 35, Folder 4)
      - Anti-Semitism, 1991; 109717 (Box 35, Folder 5)
      - Appellate Court Decision, 1996; 109716 (Box 35, Folder 6)
      - Aronowitz, Stanley, 1994; 109715 (Box 35, Folder 7)
      - Arbitration Awards, 1974; 109714 (Box 35, Folder 8)
      - Arbitration Panel, 1997; 109713 (Box 35, Folder 9)
      - Assessment, undated, 1986-1990; 109712 (Box 35, Folder 10)
      - Assessment, 1993-1999; 109711 (Box 35, Folder 11)
      - Associate's Degrees, 1991; 109710 (Box 35, Folder 12)
      - Awards (Irwin Polishook), 1979-1981; 109709 (Box 35, Folder 13)
      - Bargaining, undated; 109708 (Box 35, Folder 14)
      - Bargaining, 1969-1971; 109707 (Box 35, Folder 15)
      - Bargaining (I), 1972; 109706 (Box 35, Folder 16)
      - Bargaining (II), 1972; 109705 (Box 35, Folder 17)
      - Bargaining: Demands and Proposals, 1972; 109704 (Box 35, Folder 18)
      - Bargaining: Lehman College Material, 1972-1973; 109703 (Box 35, Folder 19)
      - Bargaining: Reaction to Contract, 1972-1973; 109702 (Box 35, Folder 20)
      - Bargaining, 1973; 109701 (Box 35, Folder 21)
      - Bargaining, 1974; 109700 (Box 35, Folder 22)
      - Bargaining (I), 1977; 109699 (Box 35, Folder 23)
      - Bargaining (II), 1975; 109698 (Box 35, Folder 24)
      - Bargaining, 1976; 109697 (Box 36, Folder 1)
      - Bargaining, 1977; 109696 (Box 36, Folder 2)
      - Bargaining: Transcripts, undated; 109695 (Box 36, Folder 3)
      - Bargaining, 1978; 109694 (Box 36, Folder 4)
      - Bargaining, 1979; 109693 (Box 36, Folder 5)
      - Bargaining, 1980-1981; 109692 (Box 36, Folder 6)
      - Bargaining: Minutes, 1980; 109691 (Box 36, Folder 7)
      - Bargaining (I), 1982-1983; 109690 (Box 36, Folder 8)
      - Bargaining (II), 1982-1983; 109689 (Box 36, Folder 9)
      - Bargaining, 1984-1990; 109688 (Box 36, Folder 10)
      - Bargaining, 1991-1992; 109687 (Box 36, Folder 11)
      - Bargaining, 1993; 109686 (Box 36, Folder 12)
      - Bargaining, 1996; 109685 (Box 36, Folder 13)
      - Bargaining, 1997; 109684 (Box 37, Folder 1)
      - Bargaining (I), 1998; 109683 (Box 37, Folder 2)
      - Bargaining (II), 1998; 109682 (Box 37, Folder 3)
      - Baruch College, 1978-1984; 109681 (Box 37, Folder 4)
      - Baruch College, 1991-1992; 109680 (Box 37, Folder 5)
      - Base Level Equity, 1994; 109679 (Box 37, Folder 6)
      - Bellush, Bernard and Jewell, 1977; 109678 (Box 37, Folder 7)
      - Benefits: Domestic Partners, 1993; 109677 (Box 37, Folder 8)
      - Berenson, Lori, 1995-1996; 109676 (Box 37, Folder 9)
      - Biographical Information (Irwin Polishook), undated, 1975, 1981; 109675 (Box 37, Folder 10)
      - Biographical Information (Irwin Polishook), 1990-1998; 109674 (Box 37, Folder 11)
      - Black Studies, 1991; 109673 (Box 37, Folder 12)
      - Board of Higher Education, 1973-1976; 109672 (Box 37, Folder 13)
      - Borough of Manhattan Community College (BMCC), undated, 1972-1983; 109671 (Box 37, Folder 14)
      - BMCC, 1992-1996; 109670 (Box 37, Folder 15)
      - BMCC, 1997; 109669 (Box 37, Folder 16)
      - Bronx Community College, 1972-1984; 109668 (Box 37, Folder 17)
      - Brooklyn College, 1974-1982; 109667 (Box 37, Folder 18)
      - Brooklyn College, 1995-1997; 109666 (Box 37, Folder 19)
      - Brooklyn College: Ad Hoc Committee on Full-Time Lecturers, 1992-1994; 109665 (Box 37, Folder 20)
      - Budget Constraints Questionnaire, 1991; 109664 (Box 37, Folder 21)
      - Budget Crisis, 1974-1977; 109663 (Box 37, Folder 22)
      - Budget (PSC), 1974-1978; 109662 (Box 37, Folder 23)
      - C.W. Post Strike, undated; 109661 (Box 37, Folder 24)
      - Calendar, undated; 109660 (Box 37, Folder 25)
      - Calandra Institute, 1993; 109659 (Box 37, Folder 26)
      - Campbell, Claude, 1977-1979; 109658 (Box 37, Folder 27)
      - Cantor, Arnold, 1978, 1995; 109657 (Box 37, Folder 28)
      - Caucuses (PSC), undated, 1972-1974; 109656 (Box 37, Folder 29)
      - Central Office Chapter, 1982; 109655 (Box 37, Folder 30)
      - Chancellor's Expenditures, 1994; 109654 (Box 37, Folder 31)
      - Chapter Chairpersons, 1977-1986; 109653 (Box 37, Folder 32)
      - Chapter Chairpersons, 1991-1998; 109652 (Box 37, Folder 33)
      - Chapter Conformity, 1978; 109651 (Box 37, Folder 34)
      - Citizens Budget Commission, 1990; 109650 (Box 37, Folder 35)
      - City College, 1974-1982, 1995-1996; 109649 (Box 37, Folder 36)
      - City University of New York (CUNY): Administrative Meetings, 1979; 109648 (Box 37, Folder 37)
      - CUNY Awareness Day, 1996; 109647 (Box 37, Folder 38)
      - CUNY Budget, 1973-1974; 109646 (Box 37, Folder 39)
      - CUNY Budget, 1975-1976; 109645 (Box 37, Folder 40)
      - CUNY Budget, 1977; 109644 (Box 37, Folder 41)
      - CUNY Budget, 1978-1979; 109643 (Box 37, Folder 42)
      - CUNY Budget: Brooklyn Colleges, 1978; 109642 (Box 37, Folder 43)
      - CUNY Budget, 1980-1981; 109641 (Box 38, Folder 1)
      - CUNY Budget, 1982; 109640 (Box 38, Folder 2)
      - CUNY Budget, 1983; 109639 (Box 38, Folder 3)
      - CUNY Budget, 1984; 109638 (Box 38, Folder 4)
      - CUNY Budget, 1990-1991; 109637 (Box 38, Folder 5)
      - CUNY Budget, 1992-1994; 109636 (Box 38, Folder 6)
      - CUNY Budget, 1995-1996; 109635 (Box 38, Folder 7)
      - CUNY Budget (I), 1997; 109634 (Box 38, Folder 8)
      - CUNY Budget (II), 1997; 109633 (Box 38, Folder 9)
      - CUNY Budget, 1998; 109632 (Box 38, Folder 10)
      - CUNY Feminist Network, 1983; 109631 (Box 38, Folder 11)
      - CUNY Mission, 1976; 109630 (Box 38, Folder 12)
      - CUNY Music Council, 1996; 109629 (Box 38, Folder 13)
      - CUNY - PSC Relations, 1982; 109628 (Box 38, Folder 14)
      - CUNY Women's Coalition, undated, 1977-1986, 1991-1992; 109627 (Box 38, Folder 15)
      - Clarion, 1973-1983; 109626 (Box 38, Folder 16)
      - Class Size, undated; 109625 (Box 38, Folder 17)
      - Coalition Agreement, 1978, 1994-1995; 109624 (Box 38, Folder 18)
      - Coalition Agreement, 1996; 109623 (Box 38, Folder 19)
      - Coalition of Municipal Labor Unions, 1992; 109622 (Box 38, Folder 20)
      - Collective Bargaining in Higher Education, 1977; 109621 (Box 39, Folder 1)
      - College Laboratory Technicians (CLT) Chapter, 1976-1984; 109620 (Box 39, Folder 2)
      - CLT Chapter, 1994-1997; 109619 (Box 39, Folder 3)
      - College of Staten Island, 1976-1984; 109618 (Box 39, Folder 4)
      - College of Staten Island, 1991-1994; 109617 (Box 39, Folder 5)
      - Commission on Academic Personnel Practice, undated; 109616 (Box 39, Folder 6)
      - Commission on Academic Personnel Practice, 1969-1973; 109615 (Box 39, Folder 7)
      - Commission on Academic Personnel Practice (I), 1974; 109614 (Box 39, Folder 8)
      - Commission on Academic Personnel Practice (II), 1974; 109613 (Box 39, Folder 9)
      - Commission on Academic Personnel Practice (III), 1974; 109612 (Box 39, Folder 10)
      - Commission on Academic Personnel Practice, 1975; 109611 (Box 39, Folder 11)
      - Commission on Academic Personnel Practice: Tenure, 1971-1974; 109610 (Box 39, Folder 12)
      - Committee for Public Higher Education, 1978-1981; 109609 (Box 39, Folder 13)
      - Committee for Public Higher Education, 1984-1998; 109608 (Box 39, Folder 14)
      - Committee on Higher Education, 1979; 109607 (Box 39, Folder 15)
      - Committees (PSC), 1974; 109606 (Box 39, Folder 16)
      - Communist Party (Teachers Club), undated; 109605 (Box 39, Folder 17)
      - Community Colleges, 1978-1983; 109604 (Box 39, Folder 18)
      - Community Colleges, 1991-1992; 109603 (Box 39, Folder 19)
      - Community Colleges, 1997-1999; 109602 (Box 39, Folder 20)
      - Comprehensive Employment and Training Act (CETA) Program, 1977; 109601 (Box 39, Folder 21)
      - Consortium for Worker Education, 1993-1997; 109600 (Box 39, Folder 22)
      - Constitution (PSC), 1972-1978; 109599 (Box 39, Folder 23)
      - Cook, Kenneth, 1997; 109598 (Box 39, Folder 24)
      - Correspondence, 1973-1975; 109597 (Box 39, Folder 25)
      - Correspondence, 1976; 109596 (Box 39, Folder 26)
      - Correspondence, 1977; 109595 (Box 39, Folder 27)
      - Correspondence, 1978; 109594 (Box 40, Folder 1)
      - Correspondence, 1979; 109593 (Box 40, Folder 2)
      - Correspondence, undated; 109592 (Box 40, Folder 3)
      - Correspondence, 1981; 109591 (Box 40, Folder 4)
      - Correspondence, 1982; 109590 (Box 40, Folder 5)
      - Correspondence, 1983; 109589 (Box 40, Folder 6)
      - Correspondence, 1984; 109588 (Box 40, Folder 7)
      - Correspondence, 1990-1992; 109587 (Box 40, Folder 8)
      - Correspondence, 1993; 109586 (Box 40, Folder 9)
      - Correspondence, 1994-1995; 109585 (Box 40, Folder 10)
      - Correspondence, 1996-1997; 109584 (Box 40, Folder 11)
      - Correspondence, 1998-2000; 109583 (Box 41, Folder 1)
      - Council for Higher Education Accreditation, undated, 1999; 109582 (Box 41, Folder 2)
      - Council of Municipal Retiree Organizations of NYC (COMRO), 1981, 1996; 109581 (Box 41, Folder 3)
      - Council on Foreign Language Study, 1982; 109580 (Box 41, Folder 4)
      - Credit Union, 1978-1984; 109579 (Box 41, Folder 5)
      - Cuban Studies, 1977; 109578 (Box 41, Folder 6)
      - CUNYCard, 1997; 109577 (Box 41, Folder 7)
      - Cuomo, Mario, 1991; 109576 (Box 41, Folder 8)
      - Deferral of Pay (Fiscal Crisis), 1976- 1984; 109575 (Box 41, Folder 9)
      - Delegate Assembly, 1973, 1976-1979; 109574 (Box 41, Folder 10)
      - Delegate Assembly, 1980-1984; 109573 (Box 41, Folder 11)
      - Delegate Assembly, 1991-2000; 109572 (Box 41, Folder 12)
      - DeMelas, Anthony, 1972-1973; 109571 (Box 41, Folder 13)
      - Discrimination against Jews, 1975; 109570 (Box 41, Folder 14)
      - Distance Education, 1999-2000; 109569 (Box 41, Folder 15)
      - Distinguished Professors, 1979-1983; 109568 (Box 41, Folder 16)
      - Doctoral Equivalency, undated, 1974-1975; 109567 (Box 41, Folder 17)
      - Doctoral Students' Council, 1982; 109566 (Box 41, Folder 18)
      - Dowling College, 1977; 109565 (Box 41, Folder 19)
      - Dues, 1973-1983; 109564 (Box 41, Folder 20)
      - Early Retirement, 1978-1984, 1992-1996; 109563 (Box 41, Folder 21)
      - Education Commission of the States, 1979; 109562 (Box 41, Folder 22)
      - Educational Opportunity Centers, 1978-1980; 109561 (Box 41, Folder 23)
      - Educational Technology Office, 1998-1999; 109560 (Box 41, Folder 24)
      - Engineering Faculty, 1993; 109559 (Box 41, Folder 25)
      - Elections (PSC) (I), 1973; 109558 (Box 41, Folder 26)
      - Elections (PSC) (II), 1973; 109557 (Box 41, Folder 27)
      - Elections (PSC), undated; 109556 (Box 41, Folder 28)
      - Elections (PSC), 1976; 109555 (Box 41, Folder 29)
      - Elections (PSC), 1978-1982; 109554 (Box 41, Folder 30)
      - Elections (PSC), 1997-1999; 109553 (Box 41, Folder 31)
      - Empire State College, 1977, 1981; 109552 (Box 41, Folder 32)
      - Enrollment, 1991; 109551 (Box 41, Folder 33)
      - Evaluation, 1975-1984; 109550 (Box 41, Folder 34)
      - Evaluation of the Chancellor, 1978; 109549 (Box 41, Folder 35)
      - Executive Council, 1977-1979; 109548 (Box 41, Folder 36)
      - Executive Council, 1980-1984; 109547 (Box 41, Folder 37)
      - Executive Council, 1991-2000; 109546 (Box 41, Folder 38)
      - Facilities, 1978; 109545 (Box 41, Folder 39)
      - Fact-Finder's Report, 1973; 109544 (Box 41, Folder 40)
      - Faculty Development, 1980-1982; 109543 (Box 41, Folder 41)
      - Faculty Referral Service, 1977; 109542 (Box 41, Folder 42)
      - Faculty Senate, 1970-1975; 109541 (Box 41, Folder 43)
      - Faculty Senate, 1976-1982; 109540 (Box 41, Folder 44)
      - Faculty Senate, 1995-1997; 109539 (Box 41, Folder 45)
      - Faculty Status, 1979; 109538 (Box 42, Folder 1)
      - Faculty Transfers, 1982; 109537 (Box 42, Folder 2)
      - Faculty Workload, 1976-1983, 1997-1999; 109536 (Box 42, Folder 3)
      - Finances, 1973, 1977-1978; 109535 (Box 42, Folder 4)
      - Fiscal Problems (NYC), 1989-1990; 109534 (Box 42, Folder 5)
      - Foreign Language Instruction, 1978; 109533 (Box 42, Folder 6)
      - Fowler, George H. (BMCC), 1977; 109532 (Box 42, Folder 7)
      - Friends of CUNY, 1979-1984, 1999-2000; 109531 (Box 42, Folder 8)
      - Furlough, 1976; 109530 (Box 42, Folder 9)
      - Gay Academic Union, 1973; 109529 (Box 42, Folder 10)
      - Gay Teachers Association, 1982; 109528 (Box 42, Folder 11)
      - Guiliani, Rudolph, 1993; 109527 (Box 42, Folder 12)
      - Goldstein Report, 1993; 109526 (Box 42, Folder 13)
      - Governance, 1969-1974; 109525 (Box 42, Folder 14)
      - Governance, 1978-1984; 109524 (Box 42, Folder 15)
      - Governance, 1986-1989; 109523 (Box 42, Folder 16)
      - Governor's Hearings, 1983; 109522 (Box 42, Folder 17)
      - Graduate Center Chapter, 1977; 109521 (Box 42, Folder 18)
      - Graduate Center for Worker Education, 1992; 109520 (Box 42, Folder 19)
      - Graduation Rates, undated; 109519 (Box 42, Folder 20)
      - Grievance Policy Committee, 1973-1977, 1995; 109518 (Box 42, Folder 21)
      - Grievances, 1997; 109517 (Box 42, Folder 22)
      - Health and Safety, 1980-1983, 1994-1997; 109516 (Box 42, Folder 23)
      - Higher Education Officers (HEO's) Cross Campus Chapter, 1977-1997; 109515 (Box 42, Folder 24)
      - History Department, CCNY (Koster Committee, Etc.), 1974-1975; 109514 (Box 42, Folder 25)
      - History: CUNY, 1997; 109513 (Box 42, Folder 26)
      - History Department, CUNY: External Review, 1997; 109512 (Box 42, Folder 27)
      - Home Study (English Language), 1979-1981; 109511 (Box 42, Folder 28)
      - Hostos Community College, 1974-1983; 109510 (Box 42, Folder 29)
      - Hostos Community College, 1991-1998; 109509 (Box 42, Folder 30)
      - Howe Report, 1978; 109508 (Box 42, Folder 31)
      - Hunter College, 1976-1984; 109507 (Box 42, Folder 32)
      - Hunter College, 1990-1996; 109506 (Box 42, Folder 33)
      - Immigration Control and Financial Responsibility Act of 1996, 109505 (Box 42, Folder 34)
      - Incentives to Forego Tenure, 1999-2000; 109504 (Box 42, Folder 35)
      - Intra-University Mobility, 1978; 109503 (Box 42, Folder 36)
      - Italian-American Affairs, 1973, 1977-1978; 109502 (Box 42, Folder 37)
      - Italian-American Affairs, 1992-1996; 109501 (Box 42, Folder 38)
      - Jeffries, Professor Leonard, 1991; 109500 (Box 42, Folder 39)
      - Jewish Faculty Association, 1991; 109499 (Box 42, Folder 40)
      - Jewish Labor Committee, 1998; 109498 (Box 42, Folder 41)
      - Jobs and the University Conference, 1977-1978; 109497 (Box 42, Folder 42)
      - John Jay College, 1977-1984, 1991-1996; 109496 (Box 42, Folder 43)
      - Kibbee, Robert, 1978-1983; 109495 (Box 42, Folder 44)
      - Kingsborough Community College, 1974-1983; 109494 (Box 42, Folder 45)
      - Kingsborough Community College, 1992-1999; 109493 (Box 42, Folder 46)
      - Koch, Ed, 1982; 109492 (Box 42, Folder 47)
      - Kugler, Israel, 1973-1980, 1990; 109491 (Box 42, Folder 48)
      - Labor Education, 1976-1981; 109490 (Box 42, Folder 49)
      - Labor Studies, 1977-1979; 109489 (Box 42, Folder 50)
      - LaGuardia Community College, 1981-1992, 1999; 109488 (Box 42, Folder 51)
      - Language Immersion Program, 1998; 109487 (Box 42, Folder 52)
      - Legislative, 1976-1979; 109486 (Box 42, Folder 53)
      - Legislative, 1980-1984; 109485 (Box 42, Folder 54)
      - Legislative, 1991-1995; 109484 (Box 42, Folder 55)
      - Legislative Committee, undated; 109483 (Box 42, Folder 56)
      - Lehman College, 1971-1974; 109482 (Box 42, Folder 57)
      - Lehman College, 1976-1983; 109481 (Box 42, Folder 58)
      - Lehman College, 1995-1998; 109480 (Box 42, Folder 59)
      - Librarians, 1975-1983, 1995; 109479 (Box 43, Folder 1)
      - Lobbying (PSC), 1978-1979, 1992; 109478 (Box 43, Folder 2)
      - Long Island University, 1980-1983; 109477 (Box 43, Folder 3)
      - Lutzker, Michael, 1978; 109476 (Box 43, Folder 4)
      - Mandatory Retirement, 1977-1985; 109475 (Box 43, Folder 5)
      - Mandatory Retirement, 1986-1992; 109474 (Box 43, Folder 6)
      - Marino, Ronald, 1997; 109473 (Box 43, Folder 7)
      - Master Plan, 1978; 109472 (Box 43, Folder 8)
      - Mayoral Campaign Issues, 1977; 109471 (Box 43, Folder 9)
      - McCall, Carl, 1998; 109470 (Box 43, Folder 10)
      - Medgar Evers College, 1978-1994; 109469 (Box 43, Folder 11)
      - Melani Case, 1978, 1982-1983; 109468 (Box 43, Folder 12)
      - Membership Campaign, 1978; 109467 (Box 43, Folder 13)
      - Membership Services, 1980; 109466 (Box 43, Folder 14)
      - Merger of CUNY and SUNY (proposed), 1992; 109465 (Box 43, Folder 15)
      - Mobilization Committee, 1976; 109464 (Box 43, Folder 16)
      - Mobilization Coordinating Committee, 1978; 109463 (Box 43, Folder 17)
      - Multiple Positions, 1991; 109462 (Box 43, Folder 18)
      - Municipal Labor Committee, 1978-1984; 109461 (Box 43, Folder 19)
      - Municipal Labor Committee, 1989-1999; 109460 (Box 43, Folder 20)
      - Nassau Community College, 1977-1982; 109459 (Box 43, Folder 21)
      - National Center for the Study of Collective Bargaining in Higher Education, 1977-1980, 2000; 109458 (Box 43, Folder 22)
      - National Education Association (NEA), 1976; 109457 (Box 43, Folder 23)
      - NEA, 1998; 109456 (Box 43, Folder 24)
      - National Endowment for the Humanities, 1983; 109455 (Box 43, Folder 25)
      - New Caucus, 1996-1998; 109454 (Box 43, Folder 26)
      - New York City Central Labor Council, 1973-1979, 1990-1996; 109453 (Box 43, Folder 27)
      - New York City Community College, 1975-1980; 109452 (Box 43, Folder 28)
      - New York City Technical College, 1982-1983, 1991-1992; 109451 (Box 43, Folder 29)
      - New York-New Jersey Faculty Action, 1976; 109450 (Box 43, Folder 30)
      - New York State Association of Black and Puerto Rican Legislators, 1995-1997; 109449 (Box 43, Folder 31)
      - New York State United Teachers (NYSUT), undated; 109448 (Box 43, Folder 32)
      - NYSUT, 1979-1984; 109447 (Box 43, Folder 33)
      - NYSUT, 1991-1995; 109446 (Box 43, Folder 34)
      - NYSUT, 1996-2000; 109445 (Box 43, Folder 35)
      - New York University, 1977, 1980-1983; 109444 (Box 43, Folder 36)
      - Newt Davidson, 1973; 109443 (Box 43, Folder 37)
      - Nielson, Robert, 1979; 109442 (Box 43, Folder 38)
      - Nielson-Polishook Articles, 1979-1990; 109441 (Box 43, Folder 39)
      - Non-continuing employment, 1997; 109440 (Box 43, Folder 40)
      - Office and Professional Employees International Union (OPEIU), Local 153, 1977; 109439 (Box 43, Folder 41)
      - Office Space, 1982; 109438 (Box 43, Folder 42)
      - Officers' Meeting, 1979; 109437 (Box 43, Folder 43)
      - Open Admissions, 1972-1977; 109436 (Box 43, Folder 44)
      - Open Admissions, 1997-1998; 109435 (Box 43, Folder 45)
      - Optional Retirement Program: Task Force, 1991; 109434 (Box 44, Folder 1)